Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Files of the Secretary-Treasurer's Office, 1939-1993.
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts(019-038, 085-089), 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (019-033), 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (034-088), 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (039-047), 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (048-071), 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Budget-Districts 1-14, 1988-1989 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts, 1988-1989 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (019-028), 1988-1989 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (029-071, undated (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1988-1989 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts, 1989-1990 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Planning and Budget Review Committee: Headquarters and General Accounts (019-099), 1989-1990 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications Industry Conference on Collective Bargaining, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Union Calendars, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Unisys Hardware Relocation Program, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - United Association of General Secretary-Treasurers of International Unions, 1992 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - United Association of General Secretary-Treasurers of International Unions, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW), 1989 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - US Department of Labor, Labor Advisory Committee, Jun 30, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - US Senate Democratic Leadership Circle, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - US West, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Vice-President's Meeting, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1960-1961 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1962-1963 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1963-1964 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1969-1970 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1970-1971 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board and 33rd Annual Convention Approved Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1978-1979 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1980-1981 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1981-1982 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board (original copy), 1982-1983 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Ways and Means Committee: Report to the Executive Board, 1983-1984 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Ways and Means Committee Reports, vol. 1 (bound), 1955-1960 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - Ways and Means Committee Reports, vol. 2 (bound), 1960-1967 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means Committee Reports, vol. 3 (bound), 1968-1976 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means Committee Reports, vol. 4 (bound), 1977-1983 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Women's Equity Action League: Awards Dinner, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Zendentsu Exchange Visit, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Zendentsu Exchange Visit, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Zendentsu Information Pamphlets, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Zendentsu/Taiwan Information Pamphlets, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Zendentsu, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Zendentsu: Formal Meetings, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Zendentsu/Taiwan Visit, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Zendentsu Loan, 1989-1990 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Series III: Files of Vice-President John C. Carroll, 1958-1992.
  - 50th Anniversary, 1987-1988 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - 50th Anniversary Video Production Material, 1987-1988 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Absentee Control Program, 1973-1975 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Absentee Control Program, 1976-1982 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Airlines, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Alternative Operator Services Directory, Jul 1988 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Article XX Cases-Jurisdiction, 1981-1985 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO: Article XX-Headquarters Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T) (I), 1982 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - AT&T (II), 1982 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - AT&T (I), 1983 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - AT&T (II), 1983 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - AT&T, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - AT&T, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - AT&T (I), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - AT&T (II), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - AT&T (III), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - AT&T (I), 1987 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - AT&T (II), 1987 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - AT&T, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - AT&T, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - AT&T (I), 1990 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - AT&T (II), 1990 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Anti-Trust Case-U.S. v. AT&T, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: Anti-Trust Settlement, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Bargaining, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Agreement Summary, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Agreement Summary, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Committee Chairs Meeting, Mar 20, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: Bargaining-Company Formal and Informal Proposals (I), 1986 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - AT&T: Bargaining-Company Formal and Informal Proposals (II), 1986 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Council, 1980-1986 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Council Meeting, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Demands and Responses (I), 1977 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Demands and Responses (II), 1977 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - AT&T: Bargaining-Formal and Informal Proposals, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: Bargaining-Koole, Florine C., 1986 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Letters, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Bargaining Realities, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: Bargaining-Status of Priority Items, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: Bargaining-Telegrams, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - AT&T: Benefit Book (I), 1984 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: Benefit Book (II), 1984 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Billboards, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Broadcast Fax Lists, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - AT&T: Communications Conference, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - AT&T: Company Proposal, May 31, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - AT&T: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - AT&T: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - AT&T: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - AT&T: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - AT&T: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - AT&T: C-Unit Clarification, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - AT&T: Dental Expense Plan Claim Manual, Jan 1982 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - AT&T: Dental Plan Information, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: Discrimination Case, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Divestiture-Issues for Negotiation, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: Electronic Picketlines, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Employee Stock Ownership Plan (ESOP), 1977 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: External Job Solicitation Program, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: Financial and Cooperation Structures, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - AT&T: Forum (I), Dec 11, 1984-Dec 14, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: Forum (II), Dec 11, 1984-Dec 14, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Health Care Action Day, May 17, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Hours of Work and Basic Compensation, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - AT&T: Hours of Work and Basic Compensation, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - AT&T: Jobs with Justice (JwJ) Rallies, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - AT&T: Layoffs, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - AT&T: Layoffs, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - AT&T: Long Lines Department, 1980-1981 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - AT&T: Long Lines Department, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - AT&T: Long Lines Department, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - AT&T: Maternity Leave Case, 1987, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - AT&T: Media Relations, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - AT&T: Memorandum of Understanding, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - AT&T: Memorandum of Understanding (I), Jun 17, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: Memorandum of Understanding (II), Jun 17, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Nassau Smelting/Southwire, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: National Agreement- Memorandum of Understanding-Original (I), 1986 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: National Agreement- Memorandum of Understanding-Original (II), 1986 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: National Cash Register (NCR), 1990-1993 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: New Expiration Date Agreement, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - AT&T: News Articles, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: Opening of Talks, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Our Pay and Benefits Didn't Just Fall from the Sky, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Paradyne, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - AT&T: Pension Plan, 1980, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - AT&T: Pension Plan, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - AT&T: Pension, Savings and Security Plans, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - AT&T: Pensions and Shareholders Meeting, Apr 1990 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: Picketing in Support of Negotiations, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Presentations to CWA Executive Board, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: Private Proposals-Book II (I), 1983 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Private Proposals-Book II (II), 1983 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: Quality of Work Life (QWL), 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: Response to Objections to Reorganization Plan, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - AT&T: Response to Statements on Negotiations, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: Savings and Security Plan, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Savings Plan-Changes, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Security (I), 1983 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - AT&T: Security (II), 1983 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - AT&T: Settlement Memorandum (I), 1989 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - AT&T: Settlement Memorandum (II), 1989 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - AT&T: Shareholders Resolution, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: State Legislative Structure, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Strike Vote, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - AT&T Technologies- Force Surplus, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Washington DC-Local Leadership Conference, Apr 9, 1987-Apr 12, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: Winston-Salem, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Communications (ATTCOM) (I), 1987 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - ATTCOM (II), 1987 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - ATTCOM: Billing Department Proposals, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - ATTCOM: Executive Committee Meeting, Jun 1984 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - ATTCOM and American Telephone and Telegraph Information Systems (ATTIS) Locals: Action, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - ATTCOM and ATTIS Meeting, Mar 1986 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - ATTCOM and ATTIS Merger Problems, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - ATTIS Dispute, 1983-1985 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - ATTIS: National Conference, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Ameritech Services, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Ameritech Services, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Anti-Bugging Campaign Petition, Undated (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Apartheid, Jan 18, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration, 1976-1979 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration, 1983-1985 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration: Case Comparison, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration: Cases-Numbers by Category, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Letters of Agreement on Transcript Use, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Reporter (I), Apr 1981, Mar 1983 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Reporter (II), Apr 1981, Mar 1983 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Reporter (I), Apr 1982, Mar 1984 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Reporter (II), Apr 1982, Mar 1984 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Automation, 1979-1983 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining (I), 1977 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining (II), 1977 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining (III), 1977 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining (I), 1988 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining (II), 1988 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: Ameritech Services, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: At Large, 1984, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining: Bell Atlantic, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Book I, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Book III, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Book IV (I), 1983 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Book IV (II), 1983 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining Chair Seminar (I), 1988 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining Chair Seminar (II), 1988 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining Chairs Meeting, Apr 16, 1986-Apr 18, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining Code-A-Phones for Daily Status Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining Committees, 1976-1988 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: Daily Tape Messages and Faxes, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: Final Reports and Ratification Ballot (I), 1977 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Final Reports and Ratification Ballot (II), 1977 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: Final Reports and Ratification Ballot, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Final Reports and Ratification Ballot, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining: Health Insurance, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: International Typographic Union (ITU), 1987-1988 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Letters from the Public in Response to CWA Advertisements, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Media Workshop, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Minutes, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: National, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining: National-Memorandum of Agreement (AT&T/CWA/IBEW), 1988-1989 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining: National-One Unit, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: National-One Unit, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: National-One Unit, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: National-One Unit, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: National-One Unit, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: National-Report, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining: Newspaper Guild-Personnel Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Public Relations Training, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Regional-New York Telephone and New England Telephone and Telegraph (NYNEX), 1986 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Regional Telephone Companies, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining Report, Aug 1980 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: Resolutions, 1977-1986 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining: Seniority, 1982-1985 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Beck Case, 1979-1980 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Beck Case, 1981-1983 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Beck Case, 1988-1989 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Beck Case: Media Reaction, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Bell Atlantic: Letter to Stockholders, Apr 25, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Bell Labs: Video Display Terminals (VDT's), 1983 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Bell of Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Bell South, 1989-1990 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Bell System, 1980-1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Bell System: Anti-Trust/Divestiture (I), 1982 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Bell System: Anti-Trust/Divestiture (II), 1982 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Bell System: Bargaining (I), 1980 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Bell System: Bargaining (II), 1980 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Bell System: Bargaining (III), 1980 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Bell System: Bargaining (IV), 1980 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Bell System: Bargaining, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Union Proposals, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Company Proposals, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Affirmative Action, 1972-1975 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Back-up Material, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Committee Chairs, 1982-1983 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Committee Chairs Meeting, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Council (BSBC) (I), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - BSBC (II), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - BSBC (I), Jan 1974 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - BSBC (II), Jan 1974 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - BSBC (I), 1980 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - BSBC (II), 1980 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - BSBC (III), 1980 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - BSBC (IV), 1980 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - BSBC, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - BSBC: Book I (I), Jan 25, 1983-Jan 28, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - BSBC: Book I (II), Jan 25, 1983-Jan 28, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - BSBC: Hackler, R.W., 1974 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - BSBC Meeting, Jan 25, 1983-Jan 28, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - BSBC: Primer, Chapter VI, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - BSBC: Resolution, 1982-1983 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - BSBC: Statistical and Back-up Material (I), 1972 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - BSBC: Statistical and Back-up Material (II), 1972 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - BSBC: Statistical and Back-up Material (III), 1972 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - BSBC: Subjects-Collective Bargaining (I), 1971 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - BSBC: Subjects-Collective Bargaining (II), 1971 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Health Insurance, 1983-1986 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Koole, Florine (I), 1980 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Koole, Florine (II), 1980 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Koole, Florine (III), 1980 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Koole, Florine, 1981-1982 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Perspectives (I), 1983 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Perspectives (II), 1983 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Perspectives-Western Electric, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Primer, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Bell System: Bargaining Primer, 1982-1983 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Settlement Guide, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Bell System: Bargaining-Work Relationship Survey, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Bell System: Benefit Plan, Jul 1972 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Bell System: Companies-Life Insurance, 1980-1987 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Bell System: Contract Ratification, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Bell System: Divestiture, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Bell System: Employee Discussion/Meeting Guide-Your Job and Divestiture, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Bell System: E.S.S. Test, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Bell System: Final Bargaining Report, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Bell System: Force Adjustment Clauses, 1974, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Bell System: Health Insurance, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Bell System: Health Insurance, 1987-1988 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Bell System: Health Insurance-Vision Care Plan, 1982-1986 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Bell System: Job Title Code List, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Bell System: Medical Expense Plan-Bidding Specification, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Bell System: Medical Expense, Pension and Vision Care Plans, 1981-1982 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Bell System: Memorandum of Understanding, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Bell System: National Bargaining-Book III (I), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Bell System: National Bargaining-Book III (II), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Bell System: Pension Benefits and Joint Program Description, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Bell System: Pensions, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Bell System: Primer, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Bell System: Status of Contracts, 1980-1981 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Benefits Plan Research, 1984-1988 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Childcare, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining: Contract Information (I), Jun 1975 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Collective Bargaining: Contract Information (II), Jun 1975 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining Policy Control Resolution, 1958-1974 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - ComKey 416 Information, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - ComKey 416 System, 1981 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Communications Workers of America (CWA) in the News, Jan 1988-Jul 1988 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - CWA Library: Daily News Summary-Table of Contents, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - CWA News Service, 1990-1991 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - CWA Organizer, 1988-1992 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - CWA Profile, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - CWA Videos, production material, 1991-1992 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Confidential Arbitration Reporter (I), Dec 1984, Sep 1987 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Confidential Arbitration Reporter (II), Dec 1984, Sep 1987 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Contract Distribution and Printing, 1981-1983 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Contracts, 1981-1988 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Convention, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Convention, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Convention, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Convention: Closing Video Production, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Convention: Press Clippings, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Convention: Proceedings and Index (bound), May 1, 1989-May 3, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (I), 1980 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (II), 1980 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (I), 1983 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (II), 1983 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (I), 1984 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (II), 1984 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (III), 1984 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (I), 1985 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (II), 1985 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (III), 1985 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (I), 1986 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (II), 1986 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (III), 1986 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (I), 1987 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (II), 1987 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (I), 1988 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (II), 1988 (Box 116, Folder 7)